<Root>
	<MiniPoop>
		<name>
			Alien Feces (Small)
		</name>
		<desc>
			A small quantity of fecal matter from alien fauna.
		</desc>
		<pda>
			
		</pda>
	</MiniPoop>
	<SeabaseSonar>
		<name>
			Seabase Sonar Antenna
		</name>
		<desc>
			Continuously fires sonar pulses from a seabase.
		</desc>
		<pda>
			
		</pda>
	</SeabaseSonar>
	<SeabaseRepellent>
		<name>
			Creature Repellant Pylon
		</name>
		<desc>
			Discourages close approach of creatures to the seabase.
		</desc>
		<pda>
			
		</pda>
	</SeabaseRepellent>
	<SeabaseBeacon>
		<name>
			Seabase Beacon
		</name>
		<desc>
			A beacon affixed to the seabase that broadcasts location and status information.
		</desc>
		<pda>
			
		</pda>
	</SeabaseBeacon>
	<SeabaseAmpeelAntenna>
		<name>
			Ampeel Antenna
		</name>
		<desc>
			Draws small amounts of power from passing ampeels to maintain power in a seabase. Most effective at short range. Not capable of sustaining high power loads.
		</desc>
		<pda>
			
		</pda>
	</SeabaseAmpeelAntenna>
	<SeabaseFarmer>
		<name>
			Autofarming Unit
		</name>
		<desc>
			Automatically harvests from mature plants in nearby growbeds. Will not completely kill the plant.
		</desc>
		<pda>
			
		</pda>
	</SeabaseFarmer>
	<SeabaseACUCleaner>
		<name>
			ACU Cleaning System
		</name>
		<desc>
			Keeps the ACU clean of debris, including excreted waste from the contained animals.
		</desc>
		<pda>
			
		</pda>
	</SeabaseACUCleaner>
	<SeabaseRemoteCamera>
		<name>
			Scanner Camera Relay Antenna
		</name>
		<desc>
			Eliminates the distance attenuation from scanner room camera signals for the attached seabase.
		</desc>
		<pda>
			
		</pda>
	</SeabaseRemoteCamera>
	<Name>
		<name>
			
		</name>
		<desc>
			
		</desc>
		<pda>
			
		</pda>
	</Name>
	<Name>
		<name>
			
		</name>
		<desc>
			
		</desc>
		<pda>
			
		</pda>
	</Name>
	<Name>
		<name>
			
		</name>
		<desc>
			
		</desc>
		<pda>
			
		</pda>
	</Name>
	<Name>
		<name>
			
		</name>
		<desc>
			
		</desc>
		<pda>
			
		</pda>
	</Name>
	<Name>
		<name>
			
		</name>
		<desc>
			
		</desc>
		<pda>
			
		</pda>
	</Name>
	<SpineEelDesc>
		<name>
			
		</name>
		<desc>
			An aggressive and poison-resistant eel-like predator found exclusively in the Lost River.
		</desc>
		<pda>
			
		</pda>
	</SpineEelDesc>
	<GhostRayDesc>
		<name>
			
		</name>
		<desc>
			A large passive herbivore with unusual biology adapted to its native environment.
		</desc>
		<pda>
			
		</pda>
	</GhostRayDesc>
	<CrimsonRayDesc>
		<name>
			
		</name>
		<desc>
			A highly heat-resistant ray species closely related to ghost rays.
		</desc>
		<pda>
			
		</pda>
	</CrimsonRayDesc>
	<BiterDesc>
		<name>
			
		</name>
		<desc>
			A small fast predator, most dangerous in swarms.
		</desc>
		<pda>
			
		</pda>
	</BiterDesc>
	<BlighterDesc>
		<name>
			
		</name>
		<desc>
			A deep-sea and nearly-blind variant of the biter. Prefers carrion to live prey.
		</desc>
		<pda>
			
		</pda>
	</BlighterDesc>
</Root>